arcadeallday.com 2019-07-26

# Game Gutter - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. Game Gutter is free for all to use, and prior registration is not needed for use of Game Gutter

No information is sold or released to anyone about visitors to Game Gutter without prior consent or a court order. In other words, no information is released to anyone unless you give permission first.

Game Gutter does not attempt to collect personal information from children. Note that Game Gutter cannot always determine that a user is a child. Game Gutter does not maintain databases of children or adults.

When visiting any Internet site, your unique address called an "IP address" is recorded. Game Gutter does not release any information about the collection of this address to any third party except under court order. Game Gutter archives the log files in order to create aggregate statistical reports, detect errors at the web site, and for security reasons. The log files are eventually deleted.

IP reports for advertisement clicks are shared with the advertiser. However, they usually have this information already since it is captured by their server when you view/click an ad. This is done to verify billing for the ads. No additional information associated with any specific user is provided to the advertisers.

Game Gutter will explicitly ask when it needs information that personally identifies you. All the personally identifiable information we collect are only gathered with your voluntary act. Game Gutter keeps all the personal information private and does not, and will not, share it with any third parties except under these circumstances:

  * When such action is necessary to conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process.
  * When such action is necessary to protect and defend rights or property of Game Gutter.
  * When such action is necessary to enforce the terms of service for Game Gutter.

Game Gutter uses cookies as part of tracking process for advertisement banners so you do not see the same ad repeatedly, but cookies will not be used to personally identify you without your prior consent.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
